[
    {
        "answers": [
            "\u06f1",
            "\u06f2",
            "\u06f3",
            "\u06f4"
        ],
        "correct": 3,
        "question": "\u062c\u0648\u0627\u0628 \u06f2+\u06f2 \u0686\u06cc\u0633\u062a\u061f",
        "weight": "3"
    },
    {
        "answers": [
            "\u0632\u0644\u0632\u0644\u0647",
            "\u0633\u06cc\u0644",
            "\u0637\u0648\u0641\u0627\u0646",
            "\u062e\u0634\u06a9\u0633\u0627\u0644\u06cc"
        ],
        "correct": 0,
        "question": "\u062d\u0631\u06a9\u062a \u0635\u0641\u062d\u0627\u062a \u067e\u0648\u0633\u062a\u0647 \u0632\u0645\u06cc\u0646 \u0628\u0627\u0639\u062b \u0628\u0647 \u0648\u062c\u0648\u062f \u0622\u0645\u062f\u0646 \u06a9\u062f\u0627\u0645 \u067e\u062f\u06cc\u062f\u0647 \u0645\u06cc\u200c\u0634\u0648\u062f\u061f",
        "weight": "\u06f2"
    },
    {
        "answers": [
            "\u06f1",
            "\u06f2",
            "\u06f3",
            "\u06f4"
        ],
        "correct": 3,
        "question": "\u062c\u0648\u0627\u0628 \u06f2+\u06f2 \u0686\u06cc\u0633\u062a\u061f",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "answers": [
            "\u06f1",
            "\u06f2",
            "\u06f3",
            "\u06f4"
        ],
        "correct": 3,
        "question": "\u062c\u0648\u0627\u0628 \u06f2+\u06f2 \u0686\u06cc\u0633\u062a\u061f",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "answers": [
            "\u06f1",
            "\u06f2",
            "\u06f3",
            "\u06f4"
        ],
        "correct": 3,
        "question": "\u062c\u0648\u0627\u0628 \u06f2+\u06f2 \u0686\u06cc\u0633\u062a\u061f",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "answers": [
            "\u06f1",
            "\u06f2",
            "\u06f3",
            "\u06f4"
        ],
        "correct": 3,
        "question": "\u062c\u0648\u0627\u0628 \u06f2+\u06f2 \u0686\u06cc\u0633\u062a\u061f",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "answers": [
            "\u06f1",
            "\u06f2",
            "\u06f3",
            "\u06f4"
        ],
        "correct": 3,
        "question": "\u062c\u0648\u0627\u0628 \u06f2+\u06f2 \u0686\u06cc\u0633\u062a\u061f",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "answers": [
            "\u06f1",
            "\u06f2",
            "\u06f3",
            "\u06f4"
        ],
        "correct": 3,
        "question": "\u062c\u0648\u0627\u0628 \u06f2+\u06f2 \u0686\u06cc\u0633\u062a\u061f",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "answers": [
            "\u06f1",
            "\u06f2",
            "\u06f3",
            "\u06f4"
        ],
        "correct": 3,
        "question": "\u062c\u0648\u0627\u0628 \u06f2+\u06f2 \u0686\u06cc\u0633\u062a\u061f",
        "weight": 1
    },
    {
        "answers": [
            "\u06f1",
            "\u06f2",
            "\u06f3",
            "\u06f4"
        ],
        "correct": 3,
        "question": "\u062c\u0648\u0627\u0628 \u06f2+\u06f2 \u0686\u06cc\u0633\u062a\u061f",
        "weight": 1
    }
]